<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.bello.nero" version="7.0.4n" name="Bello Nero" provider-name="Nessus,eQUIV,iCanuck,Kyo">
  <requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.13.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="1.0.17"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.1.3"/>
		<import addon="script.extendedinfo" version="5.6.0"/>
		<import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.3.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.widgets" version="1.0.22"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" debugging="false" effectslowdown="0.75">
	    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p"/>
	</extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">'n GUI vir Kodi Media Sentrum</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">واجهة رسومية لمركز الوسائط Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Потребителски интерфейс за Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Una interfície gràfica per a l'Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="da">En GUI til Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Ein GUI für das Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Ένα Γραφικό Περιβάλλον για το Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="en">A GUI for Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">A GUI for Kodi Media Centre</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">A GUI for Kodi Media Centre</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">A GUI for Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Una interfaz gráfica para Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Un thème pour Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Une IUG pour le centre multimédia Kodi </summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Un GUI para Centro de Medios Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="he">ממשק משתמש עבור Kodi מדיה סנטר</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Felszín az  Kodi Média centerhez</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Un Interfaccia per Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">Kodi メディアセンター用 GUI</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Kodi Media Center를 위한 그래픽 사용자 인터페이스</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Kodi media centro GUI</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">GUI untuk Pusat Media Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Een gebruikersinterface voor Kodi Media Center </summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Interfejs użytkownika dla Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Uma Interface para o Centro de Média Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Uma interface gráfica para o Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обложка для Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Uporabniški vmesnik za medijsko središče Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Ett grafiskt användargränssnitt för Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="th">ส่วนติดต่อผู้ใช้ สำหรับศูนย์รวมสื่อ Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Kodi Media Center İçin Arayüz</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Kodi媒体中心的一个图形用户界面</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">一個 Kodi 多媒體中心的圖形介面</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Това е версията на BelloNero "KODI-Leia", тази кожа е главно "мод", родена от версията Bello6 за "KODI-Krypton", родена от най-тоталното и предано възхищение към Skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck. изключителен отпечатък на Bello6 и неговата еволюция до версия Криптон. И благодарение на това възхищение реших да дам нов живот на тази кожа с тази нова версия, като се опитах възможно най-стриктно да се придържам към стила на Bello6, опитвайки се въпреки всичко, за да дам повече функционалност и нови функции.</description>
    <description lang="de">Dies ist BelloNero Version "KODI-Leia", diese Haut ist hauptsächlich ein "Mod", geboren aus einer Bello6-Version für "KODI-Krypton", geboren aus der "totalen und frommen Bewunderung für Skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, der hauptsächlich eine außergewöhnlich besonderer Abdruck von Bello6 und seine Entwicklung bis zur Krypton-Version. Und dank dieser Bewunderung habe ich beschlossen, dieser Haut mit dieser neuen Version neues Leben einzuhauchen, indem ich so streng wie möglich versuche, mich an den Stil von Bello6 zu halten, trotz allem, um mehr Funktionalität und neue Funktionen zu geben.</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτή είναι η έκδοση BelloNero "KODI-Leia", το δέρμα αυτό είναι κυρίως ένα "mod" που γεννήθηκε από μια έκδοση Bello6 για το "KODI-Krypton", που γεννήθηκε από τον πιο «απόλυτο και αφοσιωμένο θαυμασμό για τον skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck. εξαιρετικά ιδιαίτερη αποτύπωση του Bello6 και της εξέλιξής του μέχρι την έκδοση Krypton. Και χάρη σε αυτό το θαυμασμό, αποφάσισα να δώσω νέα ζωή σ 'αυτό το δέρμα με αυτή τη νέα έκδοση, προσπαθώντας όσο πιο αυστηρά γίνεται για να κολλήσω στο στυλ του Bello6, προσπαθώντας παρά να δώσω περισσότερες λειτουργίες και νέα χαρακτηριστικά.</description>
    <description lang="en">This is BelloNero version "KODI-Leia", this skin is mainly a "mod" born from a Bello6 version for "KODI-Krypton", born from the most 'total and devout admiration for skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, who mainly gave a exceptionally particular imprint of Bello6 and its evolution up to the Krypton version. And thanks to this admiration, I decided to give new life to this skin with this new version, trying as rigorously as possible to stick to the style of Bello6, in spite of trying to give more functionality and new features.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">This is BelloNero version "KODI-Leia", this skin is mainly a "mod" born from a Bello6 version for "KODI-Krypton", born from the most 'total and devout admiration for skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, who mainly gave a exceptionally particular imprint of Bello6 and its evolution up to the Krypton version. And thanks to this admiration, I decided to give new life to this skin with this new version, trying as rigorously as possible to stick to the style of Bello6, in spite of trying to give more functionality and new features.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">This is BelloNero version "KODI-Leia", this skin is mainly a "mod" born from a Bello6 version for "KODI-Krypton", born from the most 'total and devout admiration for skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, who mainly gave a exceptionally particular imprint of Bello6 and its evolution up to the Krypton version. And thanks to this admiration, I decided to give new life to this skin with this new version, trying as rigorously as possible to stick to the style of Bello6, in spite of trying to give more functionality and new features.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This is BelloNero version "KODI-Leia", this skin is mainly a "mod" born from a Bello6 version for "KODI-Krypton", born from the most 'total and devout admiration for skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, who mainly gave a exceptionally particular imprint of Bello6 and its evolution up to the Krypton version. And thanks to this admiration, I decided to give new life to this skin with this new version, trying as rigorously as possible to stick to the style of Bello6, in spite of trying to give more functionality and new features.</description>
    <description lang="es">Esta es la versión BelloNero "KODI-Leia", esta piel es principalmente un "mod" nacido de una versión Bello6 para "KODI-Krypton", nacida de la más total y devota admiración por el desollador Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, que principalmente dio una impresión excepcionalmente particular de Bello6 y su evolución hasta la versión de Krypton. Y gracias a esta admiración, decidí darle nueva vida a esta piel con esta nueva versión, intentando tan rigurosamente como sea posible seguir el estilo de Bello6, intentando a pesar de todo darle más funcionalidad y nuevas características.</description>
    <description lang="fr">C'est la version BelloNero "KODI-Leia", cette peau est principalement un "mod" né d'une version Bello6 pour "KODI-Krypton", né de l'admiration la plus totale et pieuse pour skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, qui a surtout donné une empreinte exceptionnellement particulière de Bello6 et son évolution jusqu'à la version Krypton. Et grâce à cette admiration, j'ai décidé de donner une nouvelle vie à cette peau avec cette nouvelle version, en essayant le plus rigoureusement possible de coller au style de Bello6, en dépit d'essayer de donner plus de fonctionnalités et de nouvelles fonctionnalités.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">C'est la version BelloNero "KODI-Leia", cette peau est principalement un "mod" né d'une version Bello6 pour "KODI-Krypton", né de l'admiration la plus totale et pieuse pour skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, qui a surtout donné une empreinte exceptionnellement particulière de Bello6 et son évolution jusqu'à la version Krypton. Et grâce à cette admiration, j'ai décidé de donner une nouvelle vie à cette peau avec cette nouvelle version, en essayant le plus rigoureusement possible de coller au style de Bello6, en dépit d'essayer de donner plus de fonctionnalités et de nouvelles fonctionnalités.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Trátase da versión BelloNero "KODI-Leia", esta pel é sobre todo unha "modificación" nacida dunha versión Bello6 para "KODI-Krypton", nacida da admiración máis total e devota do skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, que deu principalmente a marca particular excepcional de Bello6 ea súa evolución ata a versión de Krypton. E grazas a esta admiración, decidín darlle nova vida a esta pel con esta nova versión, intentando o máis rigor posible para manter o estilo de Bello6, intentando a pesar de todo para dar máis funcionalidades e novidades.</description>
    <description lang="he">זוהי גרסה BelloNero "KODI-Leia", העור הזה הוא בעיקר "mod" שנולד מתוך גירסה Bello6 עבור "KODI-Krypton", שנולדו מתוך הערצה "סה כ ו האדוק ביותר עבור סקינר נסוס eQUIV iCanuck, אשר נתן בעיקר בולט במיוחד של Bello6 ואת האבולוציה שלה עד לגרסת קריפטון. ובזכות הערצה זו, החלטתי לתת חיים חדשים לעור זה עם גרסה חדשה זו, מנסה בקפדנות ככל האפשר כדי לדבוק בסגנון Bello6, מנסה למרות הכל כדי לתת פונקציונליות יותר תכונות חדשות.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez a BelloNero "KODI-Leia" változata, ez a bőr elsősorban a "KODI-Krypton" Bello6 változatából született, a skót Nessus eQUIV iCanuck legszebb és legnagyobb elismeréséért született. a Bello6 kivételesen különleges benyomása és evolúciója a Krypton verzióig. És ennek a csodálatnak köszönhetően úgy döntöttem, hogy új életet adok ennek a bőrnek az új verzióval, és igyekszem minél szigorúbban betartani Bello6 stílusát, mindent megpróbálva, hogy több funkcionalitást és új funkciókat nyújtson.</description>
    <description lang="it">Questa è BelloNero versione "KODI-Leia", questa skin è principalmente una "mod" nata da una versione Bello6 per "KODI-Krypton", nasce dalla piu' totale e devota ammirazione per gli skinner Nessus eQUIV  iCanuck, che principalmente hanno dato un'impronta eccezionalmente particolare a Bello6 e alle sue evoluzioni fino alla versione Krypton. E proprio grazie a questa ammirazione, che ho deciso di dare nuova vita a questa skin con questa nuova versione, cercando il più rigorosamente possibile di attenermi allo stile di Bello6 cercando nonostante tutto di dare la dove fosse possibile piu funzionalità e nuove caratteristiche.</description>
    <description lang="ko">이것은 BelloNero 버전 "KODI-Leia"입니다.이 피부는 주로 "KODI-Krypton"을위한 Bello6 버전에서 태어난 "mod"입니다. 피부 관리사 Nessus eQUIV iCanuck에 대한 가장 독창적 인 찬사에서 태어났습니다. 예외적으로 Bello6의 특별한 인쇄물과 크립톤 버전까지의 그 진화. 그리고이 찬사 덕분에,이 새로운 버전으로이 피부에 새로운 생명을 불어 넣을 수있게되었고, 더 많은 기능과 새로운 기능을 제공하기 위해 노력한 Bello6의 스타일을 가능한 한 엄격하게 시도했습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Tai BelloNero versija "KODI-Leia", ši oda daugiausia yra "mod", pagaminta iš "KODI-Krypton" versijos Bello6, gimusio iš "nessus eQUIV iCanuck", kuris daugiausia davė išskirtinis ypatingas "Bello6" ir jo evoliucijos atspaudas iki Kriptono versijos. Dėl šios susižavėjimo aš nusprendžiau naują naują gyvenimą šiai odai su šia nauja versija, bandydamas kuo griežčiau laikytis "Bello6" stiliaus, nepaisant bandymo suteikti daugiau funkcijų ir naujų funkcijų.</description>
    <description lang="ms">Ini adalah versi BelloNero "KODI-Leia", kulit ini terutamanya "mod" yang dilahirkan dari versi Bello6 untuk "KODI-Krypton", dilahirkan dari kekaguman yang menyeluruh dan penuh kasih sayang untuk skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, jejak yang luar biasa daripada Bello6 dan evolusinya sehingga versi Krypton. Dan terima kasih kepada kekaguman ini, saya memutuskan untuk memberikan kehidupan baru kepada kulit ini dengan versi baru ini, berusaha dengan ketat mungkin untuk berpegang pada gaya Bello6, mencuba walaupun segala-galanya untuk memberikan lebih banyak fungsi dan ciri-ciri baru.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Dit is BelloNero-versie "KODI-Leia", deze skin is voornamelijk een "mod" geboren uit een Bello6-versie voor "KODI-Krypton", geboren uit de meest 'totale en vrome bewondering voor skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, die voornamelijk een uitzonderlijk bijzondere afdruk van Bello6 en zijn evolutie tot de Krypton-versie. En dankzij deze bewondering besloot ik om deze skin nieuw leven in te blazen met deze nieuwe versie, zo rigoureus mogelijk proberen vast te houden aan de stijl van Bello6, ondanks alles proberen om meer functionaliteit en nieuwe functies te bieden.</description>
    <description lang="pl">To jest wersja BelloNero "KODI-Leia", ta skóra jest głównie "mod" zrodzona z wersji Bello6 dla "KODI-Krypton", zrodzona z najbardziej "całkowitego i pobożnego podziwu dla skinnera Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, który głównie dał wyjątkowo szczególny odcisk Bello6 i jego ewolucja aż do wersji Kryptona. I dzięki temu zachwytowi postanowiłem nadać nowe życie tej skórze dzięki tej nowej wersji, starając się jak najbardziej rygorystycznie trzymać się stylu Bello6, pomimo próby nadania większej funkcjonalności i nowych funkcji.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Esta é a versão BelloNero "KODI-Leia", esta pele é principalmente um "mod", nascido de uma versão Bello6 para "KODI-Krypton", nascido da mais total e devota admiração pelo skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, que principalmente deu uma impressão excepcionalmente particular da Bello6 e sua evolução até a versão de Krypton. E graças a essa admiração, eu decidi dar uma nova vida a essa pele com esta nova versão, tentando o mais rigorosamente possível para manter o estilo de Bello6, apesar de tentar dar o lugar onde foram possíveis mais recursos e novos recursos.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Это версия BelloNero «KODI-Leia», этот скин - это, в основном, «мод», рожденный от версии Bello6 для «KODI-Krypton», рожденный от самого «полного и благоговейного восхищения для скиннера Nessus eQUIV iCanuck», который в основном дал исключительно особый отпечаток Bello6 и его эволюция до версии Krypton. И благодаря этому восхищению, я решил дать новую жизнь этой коже этой новой версии, стараясь как можно более строго придерживаться стиля Bello6, несмотря на то, что он пытается расширить функциональность и новые функции.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Detta är BelloNero-versionen "KODI-Leia", den här huden är främst en "mod" som är född från en Bello6-version för "KODI-Krypton", som är född från den mest totala och djupa beundran för skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck, som i huvudsak gav en exceptionellt speciellt avtryck av Bello6 och dess utveckling upp till Krypton-versionen. Och tack vare den här beundran bestämde jag mig för att ge nytt liv till denna hud med den här nya versionen, och försöker så noggrant som möjligt att hålla sig till Bello6s stil och försöka trots allt för att ge mer funktionalitet och nya funktioner.</description>
    <description lang="tr">BelloNero sürümü "KODI-Leia" olan bu cilt esasen "KODI-Krypton" için Bello6 sürümünden doğan "mod" dır, ağırlıklı olarak bir poz veren Skinner Nessus eQUIV iCanuck için en kapsamlı ve dindar hayranlardan oluşmaktadır. Bello6'nun son derece özel baskısı ve Kripton versiyonuna kadar olan evrimi. Ve bu hayranlık sayesinde, daha işlevsellik ve yeni özellikler vermeye çalışmakla birlikte Bello6'nun stiline mümkün olduğunca titizlikle çalışarak bu yeni sürümü ile bu cilde yeni bir hayat vermeye karar verdim.</description>
    <description lang="zh">這是BelloNero的版本“KODI-Leia”，這個皮膚主要是一個“MOD”出生於一個Bello6版本的“KODI-Krypton”，出生於對皮膚的Nessus eQUIV iCanuck最完全和虔誠的欽佩， Bello6的特別印記和它的演變直到氪版本。 感謝這種讚賞，我決定用這個新版本給這個皮膚帶來新的生命，盡可能嚴格地堅持Bello6的風格，儘管一切都嘗試，以提供更多的功能和新的功能。</description>
    <disclaimer lang="af">Muis gebruik word nie ondersteun</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ar">غير معتمد استخدام الماوس</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="bg">Ползването на мишка не се поддържа</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ca">L'ús del ratolí no està suportat</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">Mus understøttes ikke</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Verwendung der Maus wird nicht unterstützt</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Χωρίς υποστήριξη για ποντίκι</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Mouse usage is not supported</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_AU">Mouse usage is not supported</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Mouse usage is not supported</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_US">Mouse usage is not supported</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">El uso de ratón no esta soportado</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">L'utilisation de la souris n'est pas supportée.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">L'utilisation de la souris n'est pas prise en charge</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl">Uso do rato non soportado</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="he">אין תמיכה בעכבר</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Egér használata nem támogatott</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">L'utilizzo del mouse non è supportato</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">마우스 지원 안 함</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Pelės naudojimas nepalaikomas</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="mk">Користењето на глувче не е поддржано</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ms">Penggunaan tetikus tidak disokong</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">Het gebruik van een muis wordt niet ondersteund</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">Brak obsługi myszy</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Não é possível utilizar o rato</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Uso de mouse não é suportado</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">Использование мыши не поддерживается</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl">Uporaba miške ni podprta</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">Att använda musen fungerar inte</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="th">ไม่รองรับการใช้งานด้วยเมาท์</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tr">Fare kullanımı desteklenmiyor</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">不支持使用鼠标</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_TW">不支援使用滑鼠</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-Share Alike 4.0 International License</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=67</forum>
    <email>kyokusa73@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/kyokusa/skin.bello.nero</source>    
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-10.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-11.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-12.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-13.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-14.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-15.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-16.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-17.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-18.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-19.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-20.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-21.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-22.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
